你居然吃这种垃圾
Oh, I can't believe you eat that crap.
我饿了
I'm hungry.
原创翻译  双语字幕
再说附近也没什么可选的
It's not like there's a lot of options around.
最新连载海外影视剧下载
请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
仅供交流学习  禁止商用盈利
你嘴上粘了点...
You know you got a little...
不许动手
Do not.
杰
Jay,
都已经整整六个小时了
it's legit been six hours now.
你的线人有多可靠啊
How reliable is this CI of yours?
非常可靠  他说了会发生
Very. he said this is gonna happen,
就一定会发生
it's gonna happen.
好吧  就信你的吧
All right. If you say so.
我知道这样很讨厌
Look--I know this sucks,
但上一周在南区
but we've had 34 heroin ODs
就出现34起吸毒过量的案件
in the past week on the South Side.
我猜其中30起都和但丁的手下有关
I'm guessing 30 of those can be tied to Dante's crew.
那边
There.
有辆深色雪佛兰黑斑羚
Got a dark Impala.
是得克萨斯州车牌
And we got Texas plates.
好  我们看到了
All right. We got eyes.
一定是它
All right. This must be it.
我的线人说但丁的一个手下会将车停到
My CI said one of Dante's guys is gonna park a car
盖莱默街和87街的交叉口
on Calumet and 87th.
他会走开
He's gonna walk away.
另一个人会接手
Then another associate is gonna pick up the car.
他会把车开走
He's gonna drive off.
你看见我看见的情况了吗
Are you seeing what I'm seeing?
嗯  一个人在拍司机的视频
Yeah, we got a guy out here videotaping the driver.
是我们要抓的人吗
Is this our guy?
应该是
It's gotta be.
我们上
Let's go.
好  出动
All right. Move out.
我们把他拿下吧
All right. Let's take him.
伯吉斯  你守住前面
Burgess, you hold down the front.
其他的人  我们绕到后面去
The rest of us will go around back.
门开着
It's open.
上
Go.
芝加哥警署  不许动
Chicago PD. Do not move.
转回去  转回去
Turn back around. Turn back around.
把手放到我能看见的地方
Put your hands where I can see 'em.
别紧张  我明白这看上去像什么
Relax--look-I know what it looks like.
-里面还有人吗  -没有  只有我自己
- Anybody else inside? - No, it's only me.
但我想告诉你们  这不是你们想的那样
But I'm trying to tell you it's not what you think.
这和我们想的一模一样
I'd say it's exactly what we think.
是海洛因
It's heroin.
你们不明白  我在办一个案子
You're not getting it. I'm working a case.
是起凶杀案
It's a murder case.
受害人叫肖恩·韦德
Victim's name is Sean Wade.
去问一下四区凶案组
Check with Area Four Homicide.
你说你是警察吗
Are you saying you're a cop?
不
No.
我是说我是肖恩的爸爸
I'm saying I'm Sean's father.
我只是在查谁杀了我儿子
I'm just trying to find out who killed my son.
芝加哥警署
第八季  第六集
7月5日我儿子在85街和
My son was shot and killed
沃巴什街的交叉口被枪杀了
at the corner of 85th and Wabash on July 5th.
翻译     nemonini   哈里不是波特  Carolgcz
他才17岁
He was 17.
而到现在什么进展都没有
And nothing's been done about it.
翻译     四畹饭   苏葵
那一带很不太平  你们住在那吗
That's a rough neighborhood. Do you live over there?
不
No.
我们住在卡鲁梅特高地
We live in Calumet Heights.
校对     苏葵
我知道你们在想什么
And I know what you're thinking.
我儿子不混任何黑帮  他是个好孩子
My son wasn't in any gang. He was a good kid.
时间轴    Jenny 西·查
好  警察也是这么看的吗
Okay. Is that what the police think too?
警察
The police?
警察什么看法也没有
The police don't think anything.
后期     白夜君
他们屁都没干
They never did a damn thing about it.
我表示怀疑  行了
Okay, I doubt that. Come on.
不  用不着你跟我说
No, no, no. Don't tell me.
总监     苏葵
黑人孩子横尸街头
Black kid lying dead in the street.
迈过去  该干嘛干嘛
Step over him. Move on.
对他们都一样
All the same to them.
我理解你是这样感觉的
I understand that's how you feel.
但现在  我很难把你儿子被杀
But right now, I'm having a hard time
与你为但丁·拉沙德
connecting your son being killed
运送毒品有什么联系
to you running dope for Dante Rashard
他可是南区最大的海洛因贩子
who's the biggest heroin dealer on the South Side.
我想跟你说的就是这个
Man, that's what I'm trying to tell you.
我是假装加入这些黑帮
I'm just playing along with these gangbangers
好找出是谁杀死了肖恩
so I can find out who murdered Sean.
你怎么会知道
How do you even know
是那个黑帮的人杀了你儿子呢
that someone in that gang killed your son?
因为我做了警察没做的事
Because I did what the police didn't.
我调查了
I investigated.
我自己调查了凶案
I looked into the murder myself.
而那一带我问过话的所有人都说
And everyone I talked to in that neighborhood
是先知帮的人干的
said the Prophets were responsible.
你得有更多的证据  光凭这点不行
You need more than that. That's not a lot to go on.
就在肖恩刚刚被杀后  两个人看见
Two people saw a silver car racing down Wabash
一辆银色轿车沿沃巴什街飞驰而去
right after Sean got shot.
我要找的就是那个
So that's what I'm looking for.
一辆银色轿车
A silver car.
如果我打入先知帮足够深
Now if I get in deep enough with these Prophets,
我会找出是谁开的那辆车
I'ma find out who drives that car,
一旦我知道了
and when I do,
我就会知道是哪个孙子杀了肖恩
I'ma know that's the son of a bitch who killed Sean.
你是怎么开始给这些人干活的
How did you even start working with these guys?
我听说有个小兄弟叫K-迈克
I heard about this young brother named K-Mac.
发现他和先知帮混
Found out he rolls with the Prophets,
运输大量的毒品
moves a lot of dope.
于是我问出怎么和他会面
So I found out how to meet him.
我说我会汽油车  在车里装暗格
Told him I knew how to drive gas tanks, build traps...
一周以后  他打来电话  找我帮忙
a week later, he calls, asks for my help.
所以你做这些事
So you're really doing all this
真的只为找出杀死你儿子的凶手
just to find your son's killer?
他是我儿子
He was my son,
我的亲身骨肉
my flesh and blood.
有个混蛋向他开枪
And some punk shot him
让他横尸街头  就像个动物一样
and left him to die in the street like an animal.
没错
So yeah.
我会不惜一切代价找出凶手
I'ma do whatever I have to do to find the killer.
我儿子仍然和我讲话
My son still talks to me
每天晚上
every night.
出现在我的床边
Shows up at my bedside.
就站在那里
Just stands there,
全身湿透  和他死的那天一样
all soaking wet like the day he died.
说"别让我白白死去  爸
Says, "Don't let me die in vain, Pop.
别让我白白死去"
Don't let me die in vain."
我不会的
And I won't.
你相信吗
You buy this?
我觉得听着可信
Sounds credible to me.
好
Okay.
我们去查查他的说法
So let's dig into his story.
如果可靠  我们就利用他拿下但丁
If it's legit, we use him to take down Dante.
看看是谁屈尊拜访贫民窟
Look who's slumming.
你好吗  伙计
How you doing, buddy?
海莉·厄普顿  吉尔·德拉姆
Hailey Upton--Gil Durham.
很快就是德拉姆警长了  如果情报可靠的话
Soon-to-be Sergeant Durham, if my intel serves me.
-恭喜  -非常感谢
- Congratulations. - Thank you very much.
听着  我们很愿意留下来奉承你
Look, we'd love to stay and stroke your ego,
但我们还有工作要做
but we have actual jobs.
对了  给你们
Ouch. Here you go.
肖恩·韦德
Sean Wade.
关于这个案子你知道些什么
What can you tell us about the case?
不多
Not much.
这孩子14岁起就在帮派数据库里了
Kid's been in the gang database since he was 14.
胸部中了三枪  9毫米口径
Took three to the chest from a 9-millimeter.
很可能是帮派纠纷升级了
Most likely gang dispute that escalated.
只有这些吗
Is this all you got?
这里面只有一位目击者的口供
You got one witness statement in here?
有这些就不错了
We were lucky to get that.
你知道我们有多忙
You know how it is.
我们刚赶到现场  就接到另一个电话
We were barely on the scene, another call came in.
那个周末有七宗谋杀案
Had seven murders that weekend.
嗯  完全明白
Yeah. Totally get it.
但我不确定受害者的父亲是否明白
Well, I'm not sure if the victim's father gets it.
所以他现在让情报组介入了
So he's pulled Intelligence into this now.
他怎么做到的
How'd he manage that?
我们查一宗毒品案时遇到的
We crossed paths on a drug case.
他告诉我们他在帮先知黑帮
He told us that he's dropping gas tanks
卸油箱里的货
for the Gangster Prophets
为了找到杀害他儿子的凶手
as a way to find the guy that killed his kid.
我们只是想查查他的说法
We're just trying to vet his story,
是否可信
see if he's credible.
他说他带着证据来找你
He says he come to you with some evidence.
我觉得那不算证据
I wouldn't exactly call it evidence.
他因为某辆车的事给我打了30通电话
He called me 30 times about some car.
他就是这样
That's what he does.
他整晚在街上找一辆银色的车
He walks the streets all night looking for a silver car.
对  哥们  他真的很执着
Yeah, man. He seems really determined.
这也不能怪他
I can't say that I blame him.
我为他感到难过
I feel bad for the man.
但我们已经尽力了
But we did what we could--
所有可靠的线索都查过了
exhausted all credible leads.
好  谢谢  吉尔
All right. Thanks, Gil.
你好吗  拉特雷尔  我是博伊特警长
How you doing, Latrell? I'm Sergeant Voight.
我想告诉你我们已经去凶案组
I want you to know we looked into your son's case
查过你儿子的案子了
over at Homicide.
所以你们相信我了
So you believe me?
你们会帮我吗
You're gonna help?
我相信你儿子被杀了
Well, I believe your son was killed,
而且你想查出是谁杀的
and you're trying to figure out who did the murder.
对  这点我信
Yeah. I believe that.
拉特雷尔  事实是
Latrell, the fact is...
你犯罪了  而且是重罪
you committed a crime, a felony.
等等  我不是毒贩
Wait. I ain't no drug dealer.
对  但我们抓到你卸了10公斤海洛因
Yeah, but we caught you unloading ten kilos of heroin.
这数量可是X级重罪  要判10到15年
That's class X weight. That's 10 to 15 years.
好消息是你一天牢都不用坐
Good news is you don't have to do a day.
他什么意思
What's he talking about?
我们想让你作为被告跟我们合作
We want you to work with us as a cooperating defendant.
-被告  -对
- A defendant? - Yeah.
你帮我们拿下但丁·拉沙德的贩卖海洛因案
You help us take down Dante Rashard's heroin operation,
我们就抹去你的犯罪记录
we'll wipe your record clean.
不
No.
我不在乎坐牢
I don't care about any of that.
我只想找到杀我儿子的混蛋
I'm just trying to find the bastard who killed my son.
你不在乎吗
You don't care?
这是别人的儿子
That's somebody's son.
看看这个
Take a look at that.
好好看看
Take a look.
这就是掺了芬太尼的海洛因
That's what heroin laced with fentanyl does.
好吗
Kay?
不管你愿不愿意  你都参与了贩毒
And like it or not, you are part of the process
因为你帮助但丁让他的毒品
because you're helping Dante flood the streets
在街头泛滥成灾
with this poison.
我只是想了解情况
I was just trying to get information.
拉特雷尔  你不是警察  好吗
Latrell, you are not a cop. Okay?
你不能去做卧底
You don't get to go undercover.
拉特雷尔
Latrell,
如果这个黑帮真的要为肖恩的死负责
if this gang really is responsible for Sean's death,
那你应该想跟我们合作
then you should wanna cooperate with us.
帮我们把他们送进监狱
Help us put them in prison.
你跟我们合作  帮我们拿下这个贩毒案
You do that--you help us with this drug case--
我告诉你我们也很有可能
I'm telling you there's a good chance
找到杀害肖恩的凶手
we're gonna find out who killed Sean too.
听着  你来决定
Look--it's your call.
但你必须马上做决定
But you gotta make a decision now.
好
Fine.
我帮你们  我加入
I'll help. I'm in.
这是K-迈克
This is K-Mac.
我们看到了
We got eyes.
你们看到这辆银色的雷克萨斯了吗
You guys seeing this silver Lexus?
嗯  我们看到了  原地待命
Yeah, we see it. Just sit tight.
杰  你六点钟方向有辆银色的雷克萨斯
Jay, you got a silver Lexus on your six.
你好啊
What's up?
你好啊  拉特雷尔  这是你的人吗
What up, Latrell? This here your boy?
嗯  他叫杰  人不错
Yeah, his name's Jay. He's cool.
你好啊  哥们
What's up, man?
你想要多少货
How much you looking to score?
先来一公斤
One ki to start,
如果真像我听说的那么好  我再多要点
and if it's as good as I hear, I'll do more.
好  没问题
Okay. All right.
我们也许能想办法解决
We might be able to work something out.
好的
Okay.
他是谁
Who this?
但丁  我跟他说我们要见面
Dante. Told him we were meeting up.
他要先跟你谈一谈
He wanted to talk with you first.
什么时候修车店的开始做这卖买了
Since when do garage men start making deals?
我没打算跨行
I don't mean to be overstepping.
我只知道我的哥们要点货
I just knew my man here was looking to up his supplies,
所以我就帮忙引荐一下
so I figured I'd make the introduction.
这白人小孩是你朋友
Oh, this white boy your friend?
对  有多年的交情
Yeah. We've been friends for years.
-他很不错  -你俩怎么认识的
- He's a good dude. - How you two meet?
-在他修车店认识的  -没人问你
- At his garage. - Ain't nobody talking to you.
我问他
I was talking to him.
拉特雷尔
Latrell.
大概五年前在我店里认识的
At my garage about five years ago.
他出了车祸  我帮他修的车
He got into an accident. I fixed his car.
我们成了朋友
We became friends.
然后他问我能不能装暗格
Then he asked if I could install traps--trap tanks.
你要买多少
How much you shopping for?
一块
One brick.
如果感觉不错  我一个月
But things go well, I could do, like,
可以买三到四块
three--maybe even four a month.
你在看什么  老家伙
What you staring at, old man?
我就看看你的座驾
I'm just checking out your ride.
银色雷克萨斯不常见
You don't see many silver Lexus.
你开多久了
How long you been pushing that?
你说什么
Excuse me?
-好奇而已  -为什么
- Just curious. - Why?
不为什么
No reason.
我开始担心拉特雷尔了
I'm starting to get nervous about Latrell.
他不停地说那辆银色的车
He keeps talking about a silver car.
不用管它
Let it play.
拉特雷尔  你为什么要问他的车
Latrell, why are you talking about the man's car?
我们是来做生意的  拜托
We're here to do a deal. Come on.
我知道我们来干什么  兄弟
I know why we're here, bro.
我只是欣赏他的车
I'm just admiring the man's whip.
我们买卖还做吗
So we gon' do a deal or what?
我不喜欢你说话的口吻  老家伙
I'm not liking your tone right here, old man.
别叫我老家伙
Don't call me old man.
第一次就算了
First time I let it slide.
就这样  没有下一次
That's it. No more.
你他妈跟谁说话呢  哥们
Who the hell you talking to, bruh?
你啊
You.
行了  好了
Whoa. All right.
喂  我只是来买海洛因的
Yo. I'm just here to buy some H.
没人有海洛因  懂吗
Ain't nobody got no H. Understand me?
好吧  你知道吗
Yeah. You know what?
你说的没错  我错了
You're right. I misspoke.
我想我们该走了
So I think we're gonna get out of here.
走吧  拉特雷尔
Come on, Latrell.
不  我们是来这里做买卖的
Nah, we came here to do a deal.
不  我们不做了  伙计  这是误会
Nah, we're good, man. This is a misunderstanding.
我们走吧
So let's go.
再让我看见你...
I see you again...
你死定了
you a dead man.
你要干什么  你要干什么
What are you doing? What are you doing?
你想害死我们俩吗
You trying to get us killed?
我们走吧  快走
Let's go. Come on.
走吧  你得冷静一下
Let's go. You need to calm down.
你会害死我们的
You're gonna get us killed.
那个人杀了我儿子  我知道是他
That man killed my son. I know it.
不  我们没证据
No, we don't know that.
我们现在什么也做不了
There's nothing we can do about it right now.
他杀了我儿子  他杀了我...
He killed my son. He killed my--
住手  走啊  拉特雷尔
Stop! Keep walking, Latrell.
-住手  住手  -他杀了我儿子  伙计
- Stop, stop, stop. - He killed my son, man!
-嗨  别这样  -放开我
- Hey--let it go. - Get off me.
别这样  别这样
Let it go! Let it go.
别这样
Let it go.
-警长  -什么事
- Sarge? - Yeah.
我查了那辆雷克萨斯的车牌和车辆识别号码
I ran the plate and the VIN on the Lexus.
肖恩被杀时  那辆车
The car definitely belonged to Dante
就归在但丁名下
at the time of Sean's murder.
四月份他用现金买的
He paid for it in cash back in April.
你想干什么  杰
What are you doing, Jay?
听我把话说完
Look, just hear me out.
帮派内部的人说但丁
Gang intel says that Dante
是黑帮先知的主要成员
is a major player with the Prophets.
他专职管海洛因之前
Before he started focusing on heroin,
在恩格尔伍德当过打手
he was an enforcer down in Englewood.
他是三起未破枪击案的嫌疑人
He's a person of interest in three unsolved shootings.
据我所知
Yeah, well, last I checked,
解决凶杀悬案是凶案组的工作
solving old murders is Homicide's job.
好吧  但这家伙的有毒毒品泛滥大街
Okay. But this guy is flooding the market with poison,
他每天都在害死别人
and he's killing people every day.
所以如果我们抓不了他贩毒
So if we can't get him on the heroin,
就追究他杀害肖恩吧
let's go after him for Sean's murder.
这样我们就能把他和海洛因扫清
We'll get him and the heroin off the street that way.
你为什么要这么做  杰
Why are you doing this, Jay?
因为那个家伙伤透了心
Because that guy is hurting,
他需要找到答案
and he just needs answers
才能继续他的人生
so he can move on with his life.
我们都能感同身受
And we can all relate to that.
好吧  我们立案吧
Okay. Let's build a case.
看看能不能把但丁和肖恩的谋杀联系起来
See if we can tie Dante to Sean's murder.
我一直很喜欢那张照片
Always loved that picture.
要知道
You know--
肖恩更像是个思想家而不是修车的
Sean was more thinker than tinker,
但他总来店里帮忙
but he'd help me out in the shop anyway.
他不是很在行  但是我喜欢他在这里
He wasn't very good, but I loved having him around.
听着  拉特雷尔  如果我们要找出真相
Look, Latrell, if we're gonna find out what happened,
我们就需要知道关于肖恩的所有实情
then we need to know the truth about Sean.
我跟你们说的都是实情
I've been telling you the truth about Sean.
芝加哥警署认为肖恩和但丁有染
CPD thinks that Sean got mixed up with Dante,
那可能是导致他死亡的原因
and that probably led to his death.
不可能
It's not possible.
听着  肖恩是个好孩子
Look--Sean was a good boy.
我百分百肯定
And I made damn sure of it.
我对他很严厉  我想要他成功
I pushed him hard. I wanted him to be successful.
他也很努力
And he was on his way.
肖恩本来能成就大事
Sean was gonna do great things.
我全都听到了
I hear all of that.
但他是一个登记在册的帮派成员
But he was a registered gang member.
他从初中开始就进数据库了
He'd been in the database since he was in junior high.
你们觉得是谁把他害成这样的
And who do you think painted him with that?
是你们这帮人  为什么
Your people did. Why?
因为他和朋友出去玩
'Cause he was out hanging with his friends,
被扔到车前盖上吗
got thrown on the damn hood?
是你们给他烙的印
Your people tattooed him with that.
好吧  就像你说的  就算是我们的错
All right. Let's say he was targeted my mistake like you're saying.
然后他就被盯上了
Then something put a target on his back.
所以他和跟帮派里的人是朋友们吗
So was he friends with someone in that gang?
据我所知没有
Not that I know of.
他那晚在恩格尔伍德做什么
Well, what was he doing in Englewood that night?
他说他要去图书馆
He said he was going to the library.
好  那他有金钱纠纷吗
Okay. What about money?
他欠人钱吗  得罪过别人吗
Did he owe somebody money? Did he piss anyone off?
听着  我们不是来评头论足  我们只想帮忙
Look--we're not here to judge. We're trying to help.
如果你知道什么
So if you know something...
有一笔钱
There was some money.
有天晚上我在清理他的床
I was cleaning up around his bed one night,
我发现一个装了钱的信封
and I found some stuffed in an envelope.
多少钱
How much is some?
大概两千美元
About $2,000.
小面额的钞票吗
Smaller bills?
知道他从哪弄到这么多钱的吗
Any idea where he got that kind of cash?
我以为他只是在和朋友
I thought maybe he was just gambling
赌博什么的  你知道的  梦幻足球什么的
with his friends or something. You know, fantasy. All that.
拉特雷尔
Latrell,
有没有可能你儿子在贩毒
is it possible your son was dealing drugs,
而你并不知道
and you didn't know?
不可能
No.
我们定位了肖恩被杀当晚但丁的手机位置
We pinged Dante's cell the night of Sean's murder.
手机从晚上六点到早上六点都没信号
And the phone went dark from 6:00 p.m. to 6:00 a.m.
这是老手的做法
That's something a pro would do.
好  那肖恩呢
Okay. So what about Sean?
我们知道他的行踪吗
Do we know anything about his movements?
不管他在那里做什么  肯定不只是路过
Whatever he was doing there, he wasn't just passing through.
他的手机显示他在被杀前
His phone puts him in Englewood
在恩格尔伍德待了五小时
for five hours before he was killed.
这也不是他第一次在那里溜达了
And it wasn't the first time he camped out there.
我查了他的手机记录
Dumped his cell records,
他死前三个月
and the three months before his death,
他每周至少去那个街角两次
he was at that corner at least twice a week.
这就能解释他卧室里两千块的来源了
That would explain the 2 grand in his bedroom.
所以从肖恩赚的外快
So with the extra cash Sean was bringing in
还有手机上的证据来看
and the cell phone evidence,
他可能在跟但丁的手下合作
it looks like he was working with Dante's crew.
如果不是这样
And it's either that
那他就是自己单干  在那贩毒
or he's working that corner without affiliation.
这样就能解释他胸口中的三枪
Which is a guarantee to catch three in the chest.
这些都只是猜测  我们得证实
Yeah, well, it's all still speculation. We gotta know for sure.
知道现在是谁在为但丁管理那片区域吗
We got any idea who's running that area for Dante now?
事实上  我们知道
Actually, you know what? We do.
-就是这小子  -好的
- It's this cat right here. - Okay.
特拉维斯·拉洛克  18岁  不断进出监狱
Travis Laroc, 18, in and out of the system.
是黑帮先知的正式成员
Documented and self-admitted member of the Prophets.
他在但丁手下待了差不多三年
He's been in Dante's crew for about three years now.
好
All right.
去找他谈谈  看看他知道些什么
Go talk to him. See what he knows.
谢谢
Thanks.
你丢东西了吗
Did you lose something?
-站住  转过身去  -不是吧
- Stop. Turn around. - Come on, man.
你们可真爱骚扰别人啊  兄弟
Y'all love harassing somebody, bro.
-还能不能行了  -冷静点  放松
- Come on, man. - Just chill out. Chill out.
我们就想找你聊聊
We just wanna talk to you.
手抬起来
Put your arms out.
那是什么
What's that?
你带的钱可真多啊
That's a lot of cash to be carrying around.
你不知道这一片很危险吗
Don't you know this is a dangerous neighborhood?
好了  把手放下  这样吧
All right, put your arms down; tell you what.
我们可以当做没看见你的毒品
We're gonna ignore the dope you got over there.
我们甚至还可以把钱还给你
We're even gonna give you that money back.
你只需要回答一些问题
You just gotta answer a few questions.
在你之前  是肖恩·韦德负责这个街角吗
Did Sean Wade work this corner before you?
我才不在街角贩毒
I don't work no corner.
我也不认识什么肖恩·韦德
And I don't know no Sean Wade.
好  两秒钟后  我就到楼梯下面去
Okay. In two seconds, I'm going under the stairs,
拿走你要交易的毒品  听清楚了吗
and I'm getting the dope you've been working, you hear me?
上面到处都是你的指纹
And your prints are gonna be all over it.
我告诉你们
I'm telling y'all.
我不认识叫肖恩·韦德的人
I don't know nobody named Sean Wade.
你看  那就是肖恩
All right, look. That's Sean.
你还要说你从来没见过这孩子吗
You're telling me you've never seen this kid before?
这就是肖恩吗
This is Sean?
我在附近见过他
I've seen him around.
但他不是跟我们一伙的
But he don't work with us.
他不是什么混混
He ain't no banger.
他在那个超市工作
That's the market boy.
他在这儿做过几个月
He worked here for a few months.
兼职  因为他还在上学
Part-time, you know, because he was in school.
好孩子  很聪明
Nice boy. Smart.
想去德保罗大学
Wanted to go to DePaul.
你们是私底下付现金吗
Do you guys get paid in cash sometimes under the table?
对  我们付现金
Yeah. We get cash.
每两个星期一次
Every two weeks.
肖恩告诉我他在攒钱
Sean told me he was saving up
想买台空调给他爸爸一个惊喜
to surprise his daddy with an air conditioner.
他说他整天在酷热的车库里工作
Said he worked in the hot garage all day,
想让他下班后回家好好凉快一下
wanted him to have a cool house to come home to after work.
关于那天晚上你还能想起什么
Is there anything else you remember
可以帮到我们的吗
from that night that could help us?
我只记得肖恩追着艾瑞卡出去了
All I remember is Sean running after Erika
好让她不被雨淋湿
so she didn't get rained on.
-谁是艾瑞卡  -艾瑞卡·摩尔
- Who's Erika? - Erika Moore.
她有时在这儿工作
She works here sometimes.
你有她的联系方式吗
Do you have her contact info?
我可以拿给你
I can get it for you.
所以肖恩跑到外面是为了让艾瑞卡不淋湿吗
So Sean went outside to make sure Erika didn't get wet?
是的
Yeah.
那天晚上雨下得还挺大的
It was coming down real heavy that night.
我告诉孩子们我会锁门
I told the kids I'd lock up.
肖恩匆忙赶去追艾瑞卡
Sean hurried to catch Erika
这样他就可以给她撑伞了
so he could cover her with an umbrella.
我觉得他喜欢她
I think he had a crush on her.
但她和这附近的其他人在谈恋爱
But she was dating somebody else from the neighborhood.
你知道他的名字吗
You know his name?
不知道  但是
No. But...
他是黑帮的人  我很肯定
he was in a gang, that's for sure.
总有很多现金  很多珠宝
Always had lots of cash, lots of jewelry.
我不碰那些东西
I stay away from all that.
只管自己的事
Mind my own damn business.
我之前把这些都告诉警察了
I told the police all this months ago.
真的吗  什么时候
You did? When was this?
凶案当晚
Night of the murder.
巡警记下了我的名字
Patrol officer wrote down my name
说凶案组的警探会联系我
and said a detective from Homicide would call me.
有人联系你吗
Did someone ever call?
没有
No.
一周两次  难得啊
Twice in one week.
我能给你看点东西吗
Can I show you something?
-你看到了吗  -嗯  雨伞  所以呢
- You see that? - Yeah. It's an umbrella. So?
嗯  这离肖恩的尸体只有二十英尺
Yeah, it's 20 feet from Sean's dead body.
他把这把伞给了叫艾瑞卡·摩尔的女孩
He gave it to a girl named Erika Moore
就在他被杀当晚
the night that he was killed
意味着她看到了他遇害的场景
which means she was with him when it happened.
也就是说她是目击者
Which means that she's a witness to it,
但你没继续追踪
and you never chased it.
悠着点
Slow down.
直说你要说什么吧
Just tell me what the hell you're talking about.
肖恩在凶案现场一街区外的超市工作
Sean worked at a market a block from the scene.
那里的女士说肖恩担心艾瑞卡淋湿
Woman there says that Sean was worried about Erika getting wet.
所以他跑出去给她雨伞
And so he ran outside to bring her an umbrella.
那女人的名字就在案卷上  吉尔
The woman's name is right here in the file, Gil.
弗洛伦丝·克莱
It's Florence Clay.
巡警给了你  你却没管
Patrol passed it on. You sat on it.
-拜托  杰  -你妹继续跟进
- Oh, come on, Jay. - You never followed up.
说话注意点
Back off.
我每天在这忙的累死累活
I'm busting my ass out there every day.
我有一整柜跟这案子一样的卷宗
I've got a file cabinet full of cases just like that one.
每个都是黑帮枪案
Every one of them a gang shooting.
所有人都有悲痛的母亲或父亲
And every one of them has a grieving mother or father
追着我要答案
hounding me for answers.
我说的只是一通电话  吉尔  仅此而已
Talking about one phone call, Gil. That's it.
我应该打电话的
I should have called!
我懂
I get it.
但这些帮派案件没有优先权
But these gang cases get low priority.
一周左右没破  我们就往前看了
After a week or so, we move on.
我们不会捕风捉影
We don't chase rainbows.
只关注能解决的案件
We chase cases we can actually solve.
这是上头的要求  世道如此
What the bosses want. Just the way it is.
他是个好孩子
He was a good kid.
没有前科  不混帮派
No priors, no affiliations.
这不是随便一起帮派枪击案
It's not just another gang shooting.
就是这里  A栋
Here we go. Quad A.
A栋
有事吗
Can I help you?
芝加哥警署  我们在找艾瑞卡·摩尔
Chicago PD. We're looking for Erika Moore.
什么事
About what?
-你是她母亲吗  -对
- Are you her mother? - Yeah.
好  我们只想问她几个问题
Okay, we just wanna ask her a few questions.
-她不在这  -你知道她在哪吗
- She's not here. - Do you know where she is?
这是新伤吗  有人伤害你了吗
Did that just happen? Did someone hurt you?
不  我没事
No. I'm okay.
女士  我们能进屋吗
Ma'am, can we come in?
拜托  我不想惹麻烦
Please. I don't want any trouble.
不  没人在家
No--guys, no one's here.
-我上楼了  -这里没人
- Going up. - No one is here.
你们怎么不听我说
Why aren't you listening to me?
没人
Clear.
嗯  下面也没人
Yeah. It's clear down here too.
女士  告诉我们怎么了
Ma'am, tell us what's going on.
之前有人来找过艾瑞卡了
Someone came over here looking for Erika.
我说她不在  然后他
I said she was gone, and he...
他就生气了
he got upset.
你知道这个人叫什么吗
Do you know this person's name?
不知道
No.
从没见过他
Never seen him before.
女士  请告诉我们他的名字
Ma'am, please just give us his name.
我说过之前从没见过他
I said I've never seen him before.
好吧
Okay.
那艾瑞卡呢  你最后一次见她是什么时候
What about Erika? When was the last time you saw her?
昨晚
Last night.
她说她要和朋友去住几天
She said she was gonna be staying with a friend for a few days.
好  什么朋友
Okay. Who's this friend?
她住在哪里
Where is she staying?
不知道
Don't know.
最后一个问题
Last question.
这是刚才来的那个人吗
Is this the guy who was just here?
我说了我不想惹麻烦
I told you I don't want any trouble.
拜托了
Just--please.
手从口袋里拿出来
Get your hands out of your pockets.
好了  放松
All right. Relax.
我们只是想谈谈
We're just here to talk...
跟但丁谈
to Dante.
行吧  走
All right. Psh.
什么事
What's this about?
一个叫艾瑞卡·摩尔的年轻女孩
Young lady named Erika Moore.
我不认识叫这名字的人
I don't know nobody by that name.
真的吗
Really?
这是怎么回事  哥们
What the hell this all about, bro?
-一个叫肖恩·韦德的人  -从没听说过
- Kid named Sean Wade. - Never heard of him.
如果你杀了人
You know, you kill someone,
你至少应该知道他们叫什么
you should have the courtesy to know their name.
杀人
Kill somebody?
我没杀人  懂吗
I ain't killed nobody. Kay.
我帮你回忆回忆
Let me refresh your memory.
七个月前
Seven months ago,
7月5日  下雨天
July 5th, rainy night,
在你管的街角  85街和沃巴什街
on your corner, 85th and Wabash,
你从雷克萨斯上下车
you walked out of your Lexus
向他胸部开了三枪
and put three bullets in his chest.
7月5日吗
July 5th, huh?
那周我在密尔沃基
I was in Milwaukee that week.
和我亲戚一起
With my cousin.
庆祝国庆
Celebrating our independence.
怎么样  够了吗
How's that? Good enough?
我猜我们得等等看了
Guess we'll have to wait and see, huh?
这真是好消息
Now there's some good news.
我们的人找到了艾瑞卡·摩尔
Our people just found Erika Moore.
现在正把她带进局里
They're bringing her in right now.
不如你核实他的密尔沃基说法
Why don't you start checking into his Milwaukee story?
艾瑞卡
Hi, Erika.
你还好吗  想喝点什么吗
Doing okay? Can we get you anything?
不用了
I'm fine.
好  那告诉我们发生了什么
Okay. So tell us what's been going on.
你为什么躲在亲戚家的房子里
Why are you hiding out at your cousin's house?
只需要离开几天
Just needed to get away for a few days.
这跟肖恩·韦德有关吗
Does it have anything to do with Sean Wade?
拜托  艾瑞卡
Come on, Erika.
我们知道你们一起工作  还是好朋友
We know you guys worked together and that you were friends,
或许甚至还是友谊之上
maybe even a little more than that.
不  我们从没
No. We never--
我们只是一起在杂货店工作  仅此而已
we just worked at the same grocery store. That's all.
但你喜欢他  对吧
But you liked him, right?
是吧  他人挺好
Yeah. He was cool.
嗯  好的
Okay, good.
那跟我们说说肖恩遇害的那晚
So tell us what you saw the night that Sean got shot.
帮我们找出杀他的人
Help us find the person that killed him.
想想  那晚在下雨
Come on. It was raining.
肖恩跑出去  给你送伞
Sean ran out. He gave you an umbrella.
我听到了枪声
I heard gunshots,
但我没看见什么
but I didn't see anything.
你没看见银色雷克萨斯停在路边吗
You didn't see a silver Lexus pull up?
你没看到但丁·拉沙德出来
You didn't see Dante Rashard hop out,
走向肖恩  给了他几枪吗
walk up to Sean, and shoot him?
不  我没有
No, I didn't.
艾瑞卡  我们能保护你
Erika, we can protect you.
与那个无关
It's not just about that.
我在假释中
I'm on probation.
如果法官听说了我在跟
And if the judge hears that I was running around
帮派的人混  他会让我回监狱
with gangbangers, then he'll throw me back in jail.
而且我妈也会被廉价公租房赶出去
And my mom will get kicked out of Mercy public housing.
我们知道那些事  我们也能帮忙
We're aware of that, and we can help with that too.
我们会确保法官知情
We'll make sure the judge knows.
不  我不会开口
No. I ain't talking.
-我不说了  -你不说了  真的吗
- I'm done. - You're done, really?
艾瑞卡  肖恩·韦德死在了你面前
Erika, Sean Wade died right in front of you.
你得帮我们
You gotta help us.
你欠肖恩的父亲
You owe it to Sean's father,
你欠肖恩
and you owe it to Sean.
他是个好人
He was a good person.
但他死了
But he's gone.
所以我不会为了让警察开心
So I'm not about to ruin my life
就毁了我的  或我妈的生活
or my mom's life just to make the police happy.
向我之前说的
So like I said before,
我不说了
I'm done.
她害怕了  她正在假释
She's scared. She's on probation.
她不想再回到监狱
She doesn't wanna get jammed up.
或让她妈被驱逐
Or get her mom evicted.
我明白  那现在怎么办
I got that. So now what?
我们查了但丁的不在场证明
We ran Dante's alibi.
发现那周他确实一直在密尔沃基
Turns out he really was in Milwaukee all week.
-好吧  那不意味着  -能证明
- Okay. Well that doesn't mean-- - It does.
我们发现了凶案发生时他在餐厅的监控
We found video of him at a restaurant the time of the murder,
还有凶案发生后十分钟后的监控
ten minutes after the time of the shooting.
他没杀肖恩·韦德
He didn't kill Sean Wade.
但丁·拉沙德
好吧  但丁确实出城去了密尔沃基
Okay, so Dante was out of town in Milwaukee.
意味着他没开枪
Means he didn't pull the trigger.
-那是谁开的  还有为什么  -有消息
- So who did and why? - All right.
组织犯罪技术部的鉴识科刚查完艾瑞卡的手机
OCD Tech Lab just finished dumping Erika's phone.
我想有发现了
I think we got something.
发现了肖恩被杀那晚
Found three interesting texts received
三条有趣的短信
the night that Sean was killed.
从6点41分开始
Starting at 6:41,
"我爱你宝贝  比以往更甚"
"I love you, baby. More than ever."
7点55分
At 7:55,
"你为什么耍我  贱人"
"Why you playing me, bitch?"
8点13分  "你那小情人死定了"
At 8:13, "Your boy is a dead man."
就像是五年的感情在三天短信中
It's like a five-year relationship played out
-彻底玩完  -没错
- in three short texts. - Yeah.
这些短信都发自于
All of these were sent from a phone
注册在凯冯·迈克莱恩名下的手机
registered to one Kayvon MacLaine.
-K-迈克  -对  但丁的一个手下
- K-Mac. - Yeah. One of Dante's runners.
所以是K-迈克在和艾瑞卡约会  不是但丁
So K-Mac's dating Erika, not Dante.
而他嫉妒肖恩
And he's jealous of Sean.
所以但丁周末去密尔沃基
So Dante goes to Milwaukee for the weekend.
K-迈克借了他的雷克萨斯  找到肖恩
K-Mac borrows his Lexus, rolls up on Sean,
枪击杀害了他
and shoots him.
对  现在我们只需要证明这事
Yeah, well, now all we gotta do is prove it.
这样想把
Think about it like this.
我们知道有个弹壳只离尸体两英尺
We know a casing was two feet away from the body
意味着至少有一枪是近距离开的
which means at least one of the shots was fired up close.
虽然希望不大  但或许血沾到了K-迈克鞋上
It's a long shot, but maybe blood got on K-Mac's shoes.
他上了车
He gets in the car.
无论他洗多少遍
I don't care how many times you wash it.
还是能找到痕迹
You're gonna find traces.
值得一试  去把那辆车扣下
Ah, it's worth a shot. Seize and impound the vehicle.
杰
Hey, Jay.
你的新朋友在楼下  想跟你谈谈
Your new best friend is downstairs, wants to talk to you.
-拉特雷尔吗  -对  我可以说你去休假了
- Latrell? - Yeah, I can tell him you're on vacation.
不  没事
No, it's okay.
听着  我知道你想帮忙  但是
Look--I know you're trying to help and all, but, uh...
但是什么
But what?
我们不是心理医生
We're not paid to be psychologists.
拉特雷尔  你来干什么
Latrell? What are you doing?
我说了你不能过来  知道吗
I told you you can't come over here, all right?
-我们会通知你  -我去了他家
- We'd let you know. - I went by his house.
什么  谁家
What? Who?
但丁
Dante.
他只是在跟手下打闹
He was just hanging out with his boys,
和他的朋友说笑  一点不在乎
laughing with his friends, not a care in the world.
-不是但丁  -他没资格谈笑风生
- It's not Dante. - He doesn't deserve to be laughing.
-你们得逮捕他  -不是但丁
- You guys need to arrest him. - It's not Dante.
他没杀肖恩
He didn't kill Sean.
你看见了银色的车  你看到了雷克萨斯
You saw the silver car. You saw the Lexus.
他没杀他
He didn't kill him.
凶案当晚他有不在场证明
He's got an alibi for the night and the time of the murder.
那是谁  告诉我
Then who did it? Tell me.
不  我不能告诉你
No, I can't do that.
但你知道是谁干的
But you know who did it.
对  我们知道
Yeah. We do.
你能至少告诉我他是为什么被杀吗
Can you at least tell me why they killed him?
坐下
Sit down.
听着
Look.
我们觉得肖恩是因为一个女孩被杀
We think that Sean was killed because of a girl,
跟他一起工作的人
someone he was working with.
工作  你在说什么
Working with? What the hell are you talking about?
肖恩没有工作
Sean didn't have no job.
我说了让他专注学习
I told him to focus on his studies.
他在恩格尔伍德的一家杂货店兼职
He was working part-time at a market in Englewood.
用现金结账
He was getting paid in cash.
所以你在他桌子里找了两千块
That's why you found 2 grand in his desk.
店主说他在存钱
The store manager said he was saving up
想给你买个空调
to buy you an air conditioning unit.
我知道这有多难
I know how difficult this is.
但我们快解决了
But we're close to solving it.
所以你再耐心点
So you just gotta be patient.
让我们干我们的工作
Let us do our job.
如果你知道是谁干的
If you know who did it,
为什么不直接把那个畜生抓起来
why the hell can't you just arrest this son of a bitch now?
因为我们需要更多证据
Because we need more evidence.
但我们会找到的
But we are going to get there.
我保证
Promise you.
好吗
Okay?
谢谢
Thanks.
从我儿子被杀以来  你是唯一一个
Throughout this whole process, you've been the only cop
尊重我  给我尊严的警察
that treated me with any kind of respect and dignity.
我很感谢
And I appreciate that.
警察拖车
见鬼  你们不能拖走我的车  老哥
Hell no. Y'all can't just take my car, G.
跟法官去说吧
Tell it to the judge.
不  我知道我的权利  你们需要理由
No, I know my rights. You need cause.
-都写在上面了  -可以了
- It says right there. - Ready to go.
我们认为你的车用来行凶
We believe your car was used in the commission of a murder.
不  这是骚扰
Nah, this is harassment.
我说了我在密尔沃基  老兄
I told y'all I was in Milwaukee, bro.
知道  密尔沃基  但你的车在芝加哥
Copy, Milwaukee. But your car was here in Chicago, sir.
拜托  老哥  真的假的
Come on, G. Really?
我刚跟鉴识科谈了
I just talked to Forensics.
他们发现司机侧面地毯有血迹
They found traces of blood on the driver's side carpet.
正在检查
They're checking it now.
好的  还有吗
Okay, good. Anything else?
嗯  K-迈克和艾瑞卡有二十条信息
Yeah, about 20 texts between K-Mac and Erika.
就是你们想的那种
Exactly what you'd expect.
表达爱意  充满愤怒  还有威胁
Lots of love, lots of anger, lots of threats
多数是威胁肖恩·韦德
mostly directed toward Sean Wade.
听起来像个动机
Sounds like motive to me.
找到他的地址了  我们去逮捕他吧
Find his address. Let's arrest his ass.
5021紧急情况
5021 emergency.
7630南普林斯顿街发生枪击
We got shots fired at 7630 South Princeton.
嗯  没问题  没问题
Yeah, you're good. You're good.
有人
Body!
5021  各队注意
5021. Squad, be advised.
有人受伤  需要救护车
We got a man down. Roll an ambo.
收到
Copy that.
安全
Clear.
是K-迈克
It's K-Mac.
-有人逃了  -走
- I got a runner! - Move.
站住  警察
Stop! Police!
站住
Stop!
-他死了  -5021调度
- He's gone. - 5021 squad.
不用救护车了  叫犯罪现场小组来
Cancel the ambo. Roll the crime lab.
收到  5021
Copy, 5021.
有消息吗
You get anything?
我告诉了巡警车的型号
I gave patrol a description of the car,
让他们发通告
told 'em to put out a flash.
-看到车牌了吗  -没有  太远了
- You get a partial? - No, it was too far away.
他大概中等身高  中等身材
He was average height, medium build.
我只能看清这些
I mean, that's all I could make out.
大家怎么想的  是但丁干的吗
What are we thinking? Dante?
事已至此
Well, here we are.
我们的嫌犯死了
Our suspect is now a DOA.
三次枪击  都是近距离开枪
All right, three gunshots, close range.
他的衬衫后面沾上了火药残渣痕迹
He's got powder burns on the back of his shirt.
可能没料到这事
Probably didn't see it coming.
你觉得是左轮手枪
You're thinking revolver.
附近没有弹壳
There's no shell casings around
如果不是  那就是凶手把弹壳捡走了
so it's that or he policed his own brass.
好
Okay.
目前  我们假设是但丁干的
For now, we're gonna assume Dante is behind it.
他担心K-迈克可能反水  所以解决了他
He got nervous K-Mac might flip, and he took him out.
我们只需找到证据
We just gotta tie him to it.
检查交通录像  监控视频
So check traffic cams, surveillance video,
任何能找到的证据
anything you can find.
也开始排查跟但丁走得近的人
And start tracking Dante's inner circle too.
也很有可能是他们干的
Good chance one of them could've done the hit as well.
杰  过来  看这个
Jay, come here. Check this out.
这是77街的热狗店
So this is the hot dog spot on 77th.
街上的监控看不清
Street side cam is messed up,
但我们从停车场找到了监控
but here's what we pulled from the parking lot.
跟受害者说话的就是我们的头号嫌犯
It's definitely the main target talking to the victim.
你能看到那辆深蓝色的车吗
Can you see the dark blue car anywhere?
没有  但那看上去像是和气的谈话吗
No, but that look like a friendly conversation to you?
嗯  我看到了
Yeah. I see someone.
那是你和你手下  K-迈克
That's you and your boy, K-Mac,
就在他被近距离枪杀前二十分钟
20 minutes before he got gunned down point blank range.
像你说的  他是我手下  我干嘛杀他
Like you said, he was my boy. Why would I kill him?
我不知道
Well, I don't know.
也许你听说我们要抓他
Maybe 'cause you heard we were onto him
因为他涉嫌谋杀肖恩·韦德
for the murder of Sean Wade.
肖恩什么  我管那个干什么
Sean who? Why would I care about that?
我们认为一旦K-迈克
We figured once K-Mac got pinched
因为谋杀肖恩·韦德被抓  他会出卖你
for the murder of Sean Wade, he'll roll on you
贩卖海洛因
for the heroin.
我们收缴你的雷克萨斯时
You had to know we were getting close
你肯定就知道我们快查明了
when we swabbed that Lexus.
我找K-迈克去拿吃的
I hooked up with K-Mac for some food.
这又不犯法
Ain't no law against that.
那你们吃完东西后和
So where'd you go between the time you two ate
K-迈克被杀前你去哪了
and the time K-Mac got killed?
我在女友家莉娜家
I was at my girl, Lena's house.
我们有个儿子
We got a son together.
我在给他念书
We was reading books.
玩游戏
Playing games.
那真方便
That's very convenient.
我没杀K-迈克
I didn't kill K-Mac.
查他衣服是否有火药残渣痕迹
Check his clothes for GSR.
但丁  你可以不用拘束
Dante, you should probably make yourself comfortable.
你得在这待上好一会儿了
You're gonna be here a while.
-跟我说说  -好
- Talk to me. - Okay.
杰看到那辆车从普林斯顿杰转到了76街
So Jay saw the car head down Princeton then turn on 76th.
那里什么都没有
Now there's nothing right there.
但我们找到了公园附近
But we were able to get something off
谢尔兹街上的监控
a POD on Shields near the park.
-杰  -对  绝对是那辆车
- Jay? - Yeah. That's definitely the car.
我试着放大牌照  但看不清
I tried pulling up the plate, but it's all grain.
在系统里查了车型
Ran the model through our system.
是01年到04年的卡玛洛
It's a 2001 to 2004 Camaro.
城里至少有两百辆  甚至更多
There's at least 200 in the city, maybe more.
还有其他角度吗
We got any other angles?
我们直到他往哪个方向开了吗
We know what direction he's headed?
我从体育馆的监控中找到了一段
Okay, so I was able to pull one off a stadium,
但你们看  拍到了正上方
but look--it's almost directly overhead.
虽然很清晰  但几乎无法看清
And while it's a clear shot, it's even less of a chance
司机或者车牌
of seeing the driver or the plates.
在这之后  就完全找不到了
And after this, we lose him completely.
好吧  那就用老方法
All right. So we do it the old-fashioned way.
找到所有这种车型的车
Track down every single one of those models
直到发现作案车辆
one by one until you get a hit.
我们得把但丁和那辆车联系起来
We gotta connect Dante to that car.
FL修车行
找到车了
Find the car?
怎么回事
What's going on?
拉特雷尔杀了K-迈克
Latrell killed K-Mac.
你为什么这么说
What makes you say that?
我在监控录像里看到了些东西
Saw something in the surveillance video.
深蓝色的车上有个价签
The dark blue car had an estimate on it,
就像车行把价格放在挡风玻璃那样
like the way mechanics put it in the dash,
然后我就想到了
and that got me thinking.
你有真凭实据吗
Well, you got any actual proof?
车就在他的停车场里
It's sitting in his parking lot.
警长  那辆卡玛洛  我看到了
Sarge, the Camaro. I saw it.
拉特雷尔怎么知道我们要抓K-迈克
How did Latrell know we were onto K-Mac?
那不是公开信息  杰
That wasn't public information, Jay.
我不确定
I'm not sure.
你不确定
You're not sure.
我跟拉特雷尔说肖恩是因为一个女孩被杀
I told Latrell that Sean was killed over a girl,
一个跟他一起在恩格尔伍德
someone that he was working with
杂货店工作的女孩
at a grocery store in Englewood.
拉特雷尔肯定去了那里
So Latrell must have gone down there
知道了艾瑞卡的事
and found out about Erika,
然后知道了她和K-迈克的事
and then connected her back to K-Mac.
好吧
Okay.
告诉我
Tell me this.
你来这到底为什么
Why are you really here?
拉特雷尔根本不该处于这种处境
Latrell shouldn't even be in this position.
如果凶案组好好查案  如果他们找到了凶手
If Homicide did their job-- if they found the killer--
这不是个完美的系统  杰
It's not a perfect system, Jay.
我知道不是
I know it's not.
但拉特雷尔是个好人
But Latrell is a good guy.
他爱他的孩子
He loved his kid.
胜过任何事
More than anything.
他只是无法放手
He just couldn't let it go.
无法找到慰藉
He couldn't find closure.
所以他做了自以为必须要做的事
So he just went and he did what he thought he had to do.
这也是我可能做的事
Which is something that I might do.
一些我觉得你也可能做的事
Something that I'm thinking you might do too.
杰  你是唯一看到了
Jay, you're the only one
挡风玻璃上价签的人  所以
who saw that estimate on the dash, so...
这由你说了算
It's gotta be your call.
你会怎么做
What would you do?
我会怎么做不重要
Doesn't matter what I'd do.
我们是不同的人  杰
We're different people, Jay.
你得做你认为正确的事
You gotta do what makes sense for you.
但无论你决定什么
But whatever that choice is,
只要确保你不会后悔
just make sure it's something that you can live with
这辈子都不会
for the rest of your life.
哥们
Hey, man.
瞧瞧谁来了
Hey. Look who it is.
你有一辆69年的凯迪拉克帝威双门轿跑啊
You got a '69 Coupé de Ville out there.
真是好车
That is some car.
从头到尾一共18.5英尺
18 1/2 feet from tip to tail.
-你懂车吗  -懂一点
- You know your cars? - Little bit.
我爸  他以前也喜欢在车库里敲敲打打
My dad, he would do some tinkering in the garage.
我小时候  会去帮忙
When I was a kid, you know, I'd help out,
但我根本不知道自己在干什么
but I didn't know what the hell I was doing.
然后他会说  "你真是个机械天才"
And he'd say, "You're a mechanical genius."
他听着像个好人
Well, he sounds like a good man.
比较复杂
It's more complicated than that.
但你让我想起他
But you remind me of him.
-真的吗  -对
- Is that a fact? - Yeah.
他不怎么喜欢夸人
He wasn't much for praise or compliments
但是  他很爱自己的儿子
but man, he loved his sons.
而且他希望我们成功
And he wanted us to succeed
胜过一切
more than anything.
这个嘛
Well,
父亲和儿子
fathers and sons--
关系总是很微妙
it's a tricky dance.
你怎么处理枪了  拉特雷尔
What'd you do with the gun, Latrell?
枪
Gun?
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what the hell you're talking about.
我知道发生了什么  我知道你干了什么
I know what happened, and I know what you did.
我扔进河里了
I tossed it in the river.
好吧
Okay.
很好
Good.
我们只知道卡玛洛逃离了现场
All we got is the Camaro fleeing the scene.
所以你闭上嘴
So you keep your mouth shut,
然后找律师
and you ask for a lawyer.